[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Shellfish is rich in vitamin B12, which supports the functions of nerves and mental ability.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did the word Melba come from, as in Melba toast and Peach Melba?", "correct_answer": "The name of an Australian singer", "incorrect_answers": ["The name of the wife of the owner of Cunard Cruise Line.", "The name of  the proprietress of Del Monicos Steak House.", "The name of Henry Fords wife"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What vegetable is the main ingredient of the traditional Spanish soup Gazpacho?", "correct_answer": "Tomato", "incorrect_answers": ["Cabbage", "Potato", "Red pepper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie won the Oscar for Best Picture at the 72nd Academy Awards 2000?", "correct_answer": "American Beauty", "incorrect_answers": ["The Insider", "The Sixth Sense", "The Green Mile"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "And where is the lowest point in the USA, North America, and western hemisphere? I need the state and national park name.", "correct_answer": "California, Death Valley NP", "incorrect_answers": ["Maine, Acadia NP", "Arizona, Grand Canyon NP", "Wyoming, Yellowstone NP"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a celestial body, which produces the effect known as shooting star?", "correct_answer": "Meteoroid", "incorrect_answers": ["Asteroid", "Comet", "Another planets satellite"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of B-Rabbits best friend who hosts the battles at the Shelter in the movie 8 Mile?", "correct_answer": "Future", "incorrect_answers": ["DJ Iz", "Sol", "Cheddar Bob"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The bread called Marraqueta was invented in this South American country.", "correct_answer": "Chile", "incorrect_answers": ["Bolivia", "Brazil", "Argentina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this country, wearing orange blossoms on your wedding day is a symbol of virginity.", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Turkey", "Greece", "Holland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the cult comedy Anchorman: The Legend of Ron Burgundy, produced by Judd Apatow?", "correct_answer": "Adam McKay", "incorrect_answers": ["Will Ferrell", "Harold Ramis", "Ben Stiller"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much per gallon was gasoline in 1955, as seen in the movie Back to the Future?", "correct_answer": "19.5\u00a2", "incorrect_answers": ["22\u00a2", "15.5\u00a2", "29\u00a2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the real name of renowned folk artist, Grandma Moses?", "correct_answer": "Anna Mary Robertson", "incorrect_answers": ["Anna Louise Mason", "Mary Elizabeth McCoy", "Carmen Vital"]}]